let question = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question:"what is css?",
        answer:"d. All of the mentioned",
        option:[
            "a. CSS is astyle sheet language",
            "b. CSS is designed to separate the presentation and content,including layout,colors,and fonts",
            "c. CSS is the language used to style the HTML documents",
            "d. All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Which of the following tags is used to embed css in html page?",
        answer:"d.<style>",
        option:[
            "a.<css>",
            "b.<!DOCTYPE html>",
            "c.<script>",
            "d.<style>",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"Which of the following CSS selectors are used to specify a group of elements?",
        answer:"c.class",
        option:[
            "a.tag",
            "b.id",
            "c.class",
            "d.class and tag",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"Which of the following are the CSS extension prefixes for webkit?",
        answer:"d.webkit",
        option:[
            "a.-chrome",
            "b.-web",
            "c.-o-",
            "d.-webkit",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"Which of the following fumction defines a linear gradient as a CSS images?",
        answere:"c. CSS level 1",
        option:[
            "a.CSS level 2",
            "b.(X)HTML CSS",
            "C.CSS level 1",
            "d.CSS level 2.1",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which of the following CSS property sets the font size of the text?",
        answer:"a.font-size",
        option:[
            "a.font-size",
            "b.text-size",
            "c.text",
            "d.size",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Which of the following is not the property of the CSS box model?",
        amswer:"b.color",
        option:[
            "a.margin",
            "b.color",
            "c.width",
            "d.height",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Which of the CSS property is used to set the color of the text",
        answer:"d.color",
        option:[
            "a.text-decoration",
            "b.pallet",
            "c.colour",
            "d.color",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"Which of the following CSS property controls how an elements is positioned?",
        answer:"b.position",
        option:[
            "a.static",
            "b.position",
            "c.fix",
            "d.set",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"which of the following CSS property defines the space between cells in a table?",
        answer:"a.border-spacing",
        option:[
            "a.border-spacing",
            "b.border-style",
            "c.border",
            "d.nome of the mentioned",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:11,
        question:"How can we change the text color of an element?",
        answer:"b.color",
        option:[
            "a.background-color",
            "b.color",
            "c.Both A and B",
            "d.None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:12,
        question:"In how many ways can CSS be written in?",
        answer:"c.3",
        option:[
            "a.1",
            "b.2",
            "c.3",
            "d.4",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:13,
        question:"Which type of CSS is generally recommended for desigining large web pages?",
        answer:"c.External",
        option:[
            "a.Inline",
            "b.Internal",
            "c.External",
            "d.None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:14,
        question:"How can we select an element with a sepecific ID in CSS?",
        answer:"a.#",
        option:[
            "a.#",
            "b..",
            "c.>",
            "d.None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"How can we select an element with a specific class in CSS?",
        answer:"b..",
        option:[
            "a.#",
            "b..",
            "c.>",
            "d.None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:16,
        question:"How can we write comments in CSS?",
        answer:"a./**/",
        option:[
            "a./**/",
            "b.//",
            "c.#",
            "d.All the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:17,
        question:"Can negative value be allowed in padding property?",
        answer:"b.No",
        option:[
            "a.Yes",
            "b.No",
            "c.Depend on property",
            "d.None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:18,
        question:"Which of the following CSS property specifies the type of list item maeker?",
        answer:"b.list-style-type",
        option:[
            "a.list",
            "b.list-style-type",
            "c.ul",
            "d.ol",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:19,
        question:"Which of the following CSS properties specifies the stack order of elements?",
        answer:"z-index",
        option:[
            "a.z-index",
            "b.overlap",
            "c.No such specific property is present",
            "d.None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:20,
        question:"What value should be passed to the width parameter if we want an elements,say a table,to span the entire width of the screen?",
        answer:"a.100%",
        option:[
            "a.100%",
            "b.75%",
            "c.50%",
            "d.0%",
        ]
    }
]